So we looked at how to build our very first console application.
所以，我们研究了如何构建我们的第一个控制台应用程序
And one of the great things about the .NET community is
另外有一好消息，我们在 .NET 社区中
about the documentation that we have right now.
已经有了相关的文档
There's a lot of great docs and I know it's silly sometimes
这有许多的优秀文档
to talk about how great the docs are.
我想不用再介绍这些文档有多棒了（误）
But really the docs are very, very good.
但这些文档真的非常非常好
If you go to docs.microsoft.com we can click on .NET, or
如果你转到 docs.microsoft.com，我们可以点击 .NET
you can go /.NET, there's a ton of documentation here.
或者你可以转到 /dotnet，这有大量有关的文档。
There's the .NET Core Guide, which will have tutorials, it'll
这是 .NET Core 指南，其中包含了教程
talk about ASP.NET Core that we're gonna talk about as well.
它将会讲述我们接下来要探讨的 ASP.NET Core
And it's worth pointing out the difference between the .NET
值得指出的是，.NET指南
Core Guide and then the language guides.
和编程语言指南是不同的
Yep and then you'll see there are different language guides.
对，你可以看到这有不同语言的指南
We have VB, we have C#, we have F#.
比如 VB,C#, 以及 F#
Right, so
正是如此
these are the guides that will give you understanding of
这些指南将会帮助你理解
the syntax of the language.
语言的语法
Yep
对的
And how to call the methods, and
包括如何去调用一个方法
then the .NET core framework itself.
以及 .NET Core 这个框架本身
And all of those methods are available from C#,
所有的这些方法都可以在 C#,F#
F# and in Visual Basic
以及 Visual Basic 中调用
And it's really important for
这真的非常重要
people to actually learn the language a little bit more,
我们一般是先学习某一语言
before they start looking at the platform itself.
然后才开始了解平台本身
Absolutely, absolutely
当然如此
And we did a hello world, I installed the .NET core SDK.
我们此前做了一个 Hello World，我安装了 .NET Core SDK
And I ran it from the command line, and
我通过命令行运行了这个程序
then I opened it up in Visual Studio code.
然后我通过 Visual Studio Code 打开这个项目
Do I have to install that stuff to say hello world?
我必须安装那些东西才能出现 "Hello World" 吗？
No you don't anymore
不，你不必这样了
we actually have something right in the documentation.
实际上，在文档中我们已经有正确的方式
If you go over to Quick Starts under C#.
如果你转到 C# 的 Quick Starts
So C#
那么，C#
Quick Starts, it will drop you right into the Quick Start page.
Quick Starts, 它会直接进入 Quick Starts 的页面
And this shows you from the hello world experience
它会向你展示 Hello World 的体验
how to get started with numbers in C#, declaring variables.
如何开始在 C# 中使用数字，声明变量
It shows you some really fun examples that you can start
这将是非常有趣的示例，你可以
playing around to it, so if you, I've got
从这里开始体验，如果你 我已经
a .NET editor here in my browser.
在我的浏览器中有一个 .NET 编辑器了
Yeah
好的
I'll go and copy Console.WriteLine over here
我将从这里拷贝 Console.WriteLine()
Yep, or you can just click on the Copy as well.
或者，你也可以点击 Copy 按钮
Okay, click on Copy, hit Run.
好吧，点击 Copy 点击 Run
And now it's running in the cloud, and
现在它运行在云端
it brought the result over here.
这里将显示它的结果
So the .NET SDK is not installed on my machine.
所以 .NET SDK 并没有安装在我的电脑上
No. It's happening right here.
没有 可它正在这里运行。
Exactly and you can go in, and edit that and maybe.
确切地说，你可以进去，编辑它
Mm-hm so I can make changes to this kind of code.
Emmm 所以我可以改动这些代码
I can do whatever I want and
我可以做任何我想做的
then the output will appear down here.
且输出将会出现在这里
Absolutely
当然喽
And I can mess with,
我还可以更复杂一些
look at this I can do all kinds of fancy stuffs.
看看这些，我可以做各种花哨的东西
So if I bring in really complicated code and
所以如果我使用非常复杂的代码
mess with strings
且与字符串混在一起
Yeah. And do that, and
嗯。运行这些，然后
follow through with some online challenges
完成一些在线挑战
So it's actually designed as a complete challenge,
所以，它实际上被设计成一个完整的挑战
that's supposed to take 20 minutes at the very most.
这应该最多只需20分钟。
Step by steps,
一步一步来
gives you examples of what needs to be done.
给你一些示例，说明需要做什么
The editor that's working in the browser right now is in preview.
现在在浏览器中的编辑器仍在预览中
So if people see any bugs, we're really excited for
所以如果人们发现任何错误，我们真的很
you guys to give us any feedback then.
期待你们给我们的任何反馈
Sure and then you can report those on the GitHub repository.
当然，然后你可以在 GitHub 存储库上报告
Sure and then you can report those on the GitHub repository
Yeah. And speaking of GitHub
是的。谈到 GitHub
in fact all of .NET is open source so
事实上 .NET 的所有都是开源的
it's important to remember that it is all on GitHub.
这一切都在 GitHub 上，记住这点很重要
So if you go to github.com/dotnet
所以如果你去 github.com/dotnet
you'll come here to .NET foundation and
你会看到 .NET 基金会以及
it is within there that all the source code is there.
所有源代码都在那里
Now as a beginner you might not necessarily care about that
现在作为初学者，你可能不需要关心
source code, but it's just nice to now it's there.
源代码，但开源终究是件好事
Yeah, and they also do have samples within most of
对的，在大部分的代码库中都有示例
the repos, so they can start playing around
所以大家从这儿开始
Actually that is a good point
的确，这是一个好主意
It's all there, you can go and look at the, coreclr and
所有的东西都在那儿，你可以去看 coreclr 和
the docs themselves are also open-source.
文档本身也是开源的
Yes they are, so if you see any typos, if you see any
是的，所以如果你看到任何错别字，以及
options as you'd like to look at, you could do that
你想看看的选项，你可以这样做
So if you click on the edit over there
如果你点击那边的编辑
So I'm here on, for example, getting started with .NET Core.
我在这个页面，例如，开始使用.NET Core
Yeah. And you said click on Edit
嗯。 你说过点击编辑
where do I end up at?
我最终在哪里？
Well I end up at GitHub
那么我最终在GitHub页面上
Yep
是的
So I can be a contributor to open source
所以我可以成为开源的贡献者
by even fixing a spelling error
甚至修复拼写错误
Or changing a bit of code that may be incorrect
或者改写一些可能不正确的代码
Exactly. All right.
没错 好的
All of this is under the .NET Foundation GitHub.
所有这些都在GitHub的.NET基金会下
And you can also check out the .NET Foundation at
你也可以在 www.dotnetfoundation.org 上
www.dotnetfoundation.org.
查看 .NET 基金会
There you are.
看，你在这
There I am. You just flew by there.
哦，这是我。 你刚刚从那里飞过。
So the .NET Foundation is a non-profit, an independent
所以 .NET 基金会是一个非盈利的，独立的
non-profit, that tries to support the .NET ecosystem.
它正支持着 .NET 的生态。
All right?
嗯？
There's lots of open source projects that are within it.
其中有很多开源项目
You can set up a local Meetup or find a local Meetup near you.
你可以举办本地聚会或在你附近找到本地聚会
We've got Meetups all over the world.
我们也在世界各地举办了聚会
Wow
Literally all over the world.
差不多遍布全世界
We really do, actually
实际上，我们真的这样做了
And There's one on every continent and
而且每个大洲都有一个
you also have a show.
你也有一个节目
Yep Called code conversation.
是的 叫做 Code Conversation
Yeah, the weird thing about code conversations, is it's five
对，关于 Code Conversation 的特别之处是
to ten minute videos, that we seat down with engineers or
它是五到十分钟的视频，我们与工程师或者
people working in different open source projects.
在不同的开源项目中的人一起坐下来
And they tell us a little bit of how to get started on
他们会告诉我们一些如何开始
that project
项目的经历
Mm-hm
嗯
So you can check that out, that's on YouTube and
所以你可以来看看，这会在在 YouTube 上放送
also on Channel 9, which is our TV channel
当然 Channel 9 也会有，这是我们的电视频道
And again I wanna encourage people to check
再次，我想鼓励大家
out the meet ups
都来看看这个会议
There's about 1200 different meet ups locally
在各地约有1200种不同的聚会
user groups they're not locally, rather world wide.
参会者不光是来自本地的，而是来自全世界
You can learn open source, you can sit and find friends to
你可以学习开源（项目），坐下来找个朋友
code with, you can pair up, you can do all kinds of things
一起写代码，组队，做各种事情
And if there is no one nearby you
如果你附近没有聚会
you could even potentially Skype people.
你甚至可以通过 Skype 参与
That's actually a good idea
这真是一个好主意
A Skype meet up
一个 Skype 聚会
I do that all of the time.
我一直这么做
I have lots of different opportunities where I sit with
我有很多不同的机会来和人们坐在一起
people and learn code, and pair, but what we do remotely.
学习代码，组队，但我们远程该怎么做
And you can do that with Skype interviews as well?
你也可以通过 Skype 访谈来做到这一点？
That's true, all right
没错，好
So just a reminder, you can go to docs.microsoft.com, check out
所以只是提醒一下，你可以去 docs.microsoft.com，看看
the Quick Starts to run your C# programs in the browser.
快速入门，且在浏览器中运行 C＃ 程序
Also a great way to maybe introduce your young people or
这也是一个很好的方式来介绍小白或者
new programmers to coding in C#.
刚入门的程序员来使用 C＃ 编写代码
And then if you start at either GitHub or the .NET Foundation,
然后，如果您从 GitHub 或 .NET Foundation 开始，
you can jump off to all of these different locations.
你可以跳转到所有这些不同的页面
And then one other thing worth pointing out,
还有一件事值得指出
As I just saw it fly by, was a .NET Conf.
我刚刚看到它飞过，是 .NET Conf
Yep
是的
there is a lot of great content that came out of .NET Conf.
.NET Conf 上会有很多很棒的内容
Mm-hm
嗯
This was a conference in 2017
这是2017年的一次会议
And you can go and check out the sessions for
你可以去看看 .NET Conf 的活动
.NET Conf up here at dotnetconf.net
在 dotnetconf.net 上可以找到
There were 45 different sessions
有45个不同的会议
About 45 hours of content
大约45小时的内容
that you can learn some of the more advanced techniques.
你可以学习一些更先进的技术
Yeah So
是的 那么
when you're done here at Microsoft Virtual Academy,
当您在微软虚拟学院完成此任务时
you can maybe dig into that more advanced stuff.
你可以去发掘更先进的东西了
Exactly. All right
没错。 好的
take a quick break, we'll come back and make a web application.
稍作休息，我们会回来做一个 Web 应用
Yes we will.
是的，我们会的